Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art public programs records, circa 1995-2011 COR0003.5.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Program files, financial records, and calendar productions, 1994-2011; Series 1
  - Light, Color, and Paint, Oh My! Family Workshop, 2011 August 20; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 77)
  - Sculpt It!, 2011 June 18; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 78)
  - Scholar's Selection Gallery Talks, 2011 April; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 79)
  - Mona Hajj: Interior Visions, 2011 April 20; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 80)
  - Textiles Travels; John Robshaw, 2011 May 25; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 81)
- Events, 2004-2008; Series 2
  Arranged in original order.
  - May-July 2004 Newspaper Clippings, 2004 May-July; Series 2 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - 2004 June Public Programs FY2004, Series 2 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - 2004 April-May Newspaper Clippings, Series 2 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - 2004 April Public Programs FY04, Series 2 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - May 2004 Newspaper Clippings, 2004 May; Series 2 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - L870 May 20, 2004 FY2004 Dana Ivey CANCELED, 2004 May 20; Series 2 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - 2004 May Public Programs FY04, Series 2 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - A Walk into the Sea - Esther Robinson, 2008 October 20; Series 2 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Tour to Barnes Baltimore, 2008 October 17; Series 2 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Shepard Fairey Al Farrow, 2008 October 17; Series 2 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Presenting Timothy Greenfield Sanders, 2008 October 16; Series 2 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Reconstitution 2008 50-50 Limited, 2008 October 15; Series 2 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - To Wit: Rosson-Wry Funny Songs Steve Ross, 2008 October 6; Series 2 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Shadow of the House Abelardo Morrell Allie Humenuk, 2008 October 1; Series 2 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Architecture Urbanism in Barcelona, 2008 September 30; Series 2 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Richard Avedon: An Evening With Curators Frank Goodyear and Paul Roth, 2008 September 25; Series 2 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - The Forger's Spell Edward Dolnick, 2008 September 24; Series 2 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Design in Spain Now Julicapella Martin Azua, 2008 September 23; Series 2 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Wine Goes Green Brett Freeman, 2008 September 22; Series 2 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - CMF Verge Ensemble, 2008 September 21; Series 2 (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - Taking the Cake Duff Goldman, 2008 September 18; Series 2 (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - French Pianist Benoit Delbecq, 2008 September 17; Series 2 (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - The Oxford Project, 2008 September 16; Series 2 (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - No Wave Thurston Moore/Byron Coley, 2008 July 29; Series 2 (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - Contemporary Art Tour to NYC, 2008 July 25; Series 2 (Box 65, Folder 18)
  - Eccentric Glamour Simon Doonan, 2008 July 24; Series 2 (Box 65, Folder 19)
  - Fallingwater Bus Tour, 2008 July 18; Series 2 (Box 65, Folder 20)
  - Ten Canonical Buildings Peter Eisenman, 2008 July 16; Series 2 (Box 65, Folder 21)
  - Defining the New Cool Michael Hirschorn, 2008 July 15; Series 2 (Box 65, Folder 22)
  - Cold Blooded Stephen Hunter, 2008 July 10; Series 2 (Box 65, Folder 23)
  - Low Rent High Style Nick Olsen, 2008 June 26; Series 2 (Box 65, Folder 24)
  - Iced, Art Deco Diamonds Design Dino Pampillonia, 2008 June 25; Series 2 (Box 65, Folder 25)
  - Stretch Your Imagination Rebecca Gitter, 2008 June 22; Series 2 (Box 65, Folder 26)
  - Curator's Choice Gallery Talk Sarah Cash, 2008 June 19; Series 2 (Box 65, Folder 27)
  - Cool Hues Gallery Talk, 2008 June 12; Series 2 (Box 65, Folder 28)
  - Antiques Road Trip, 2008 June 11; Series 2 (Box 65, Folder 29)
  - Brendan James, 2008 June 10; Series 2 (Box 65, Folder 30)
  - John Gruen: Callas Kissed Me... Lenny Too!, 2008 June 9; Series 2 (Box 65, Folder 31)
  - Did Your Mother Come From Ireland? Patrick Clerkin Lillian O'Connell, 2008 June 8; Series 2 (Box 65, Folder 32)
  - American Women Artists Nancy Heller, 2008 June 3; Series 2 (Box 65, Folder 33)
  - MES: Ebene Quartet, 2008 May 30; Series 2 (Box 65, Folder 34)
  - Cartography Tour, 2008 May 21; Series 2 (Box 65, Folder 35)
  - Standard Operating Procedure Nubar Alexanian, 2008 May 20; Series 2 (Box 65, Folder 36)
  - Curator's Choice Series Emily Shapiro, 2008 May 15; Series 2 (Box 65, Folder 37)
  - Dudley Lecture Women Adelson on Sargent, 2008 May 12; Series 2 (Box 65, Folder 38)
  - MES: Klavier Trio Amsterdam, 2008 May 9; Series 2 (Box 65, Folder 39)
  - From the Runway to Reality, 2008 May 6; Series 2 (Box 65, Folder 40)
  - An American Road Trip, 2008 May 7; Series 2 (Box 65, Folder 41)
  - Mt. Pleasant: An Unexpected Village in the City, 2008 May 2; Series 2 (Box 65, Folder 42)
  - Verge Ensemble, 2008 April 27; Series 2 (Box 65, Folder 43)
  - MES: Walden Chamber Players, 2008 April 25; Series 2 (Box 65, Folder 44)
  - Evidence of my Existence Jim Lo Scalzo, 2008 April 23; Series 2 (Box 65, Folder 45)
  - Sarah Newman Gallery Talk, 2008 April 10; Series 2 (Box 65, Folder 46)
  - Ziva's Spanish Dance Ensemble, 2008 April 9; Series 2 (Box 65, Folder 47)
- Musical Evening Series, 1996-2005; Series 3
  General
  Series 1 contains records for the Musical Evening series. Often abreviated in folder titles as MES.
  - Contracts, 1997-1998; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - MES 1997-1998, Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - 1997-1998 MES Subscriptions, Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Programs, Circa 1996-1999; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - The Takacs String Quartet, 1998 January 30; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - The Eroica Trio, 1997 October 24; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Regular Subscribers MES, 1997-1998; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - The St. Lawrence String Quartet, 1998 February 28; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Marcy Rosen Friends, 1998 April 10; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - The Angeles String Quartet, 1997 November 14; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - The Brentano String Quartet, 1998 May 15; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - The Borromeo String Quartet, 1998 March 20; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Goff/Alper/Joseph, Circa 1996-1999; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Circle Subscribers MES, 1997-1998; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Audubon, Circa 1996-1999; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Loose Documents, Circa 1996-1999; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - MES Program Notes, 1997-1998; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - MES Program, 1997-1998; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - MES Stuff, Circa 1996-1999; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Reversed Signs, Circa 1996-1999; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - MES Files on Disk, Circa 1996-1999; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Musical Evening Series, Circa 1996-1999; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - MES 98-99, 1998-1999; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Alper, Burstein, Joseph etc, 1997-1998; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - MES Dinner, 1997-1998; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - MES Forms, Circa 1996-1999; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - MES Correspondence, Circa 1996-1999; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Mes Schedule 1973-present, Series 3 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - MES 1995-1996, Series 3 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - MES 1995-1996 Advertising, Series 3 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - MES 1995-1996 Brochure, Series 3 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - MES 1995-1996 Budget, Series 3 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - MES 1995-1996 Committee, Series 3 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - MES 1995-1996 Day of Con, Series 3 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - MES 1995-1996 Dinner, Series 3 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Prg Notes 1995-1996, Series 3 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - MES 1996-1997, Series 3 (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - MES 1997-1998, Series 3 (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - MES 1999-2000, Series 3 (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - MES 1999-2000 Correspondence, Series 3 (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - MES 1999-2000 Max's, Series 3 (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - MES 1999-2000 Wash. Post, Series 3 (Box 67, Folder 15)
  - MES 1999-2000 Mindy's, Series 3 (Box 67, Folder 16)
  - MES 2000-2001 Post-Events, Series 3 (Box 67, Folder 17)
  - MES 2000-2001 Programs/P. Notes, Series 3 (Box 67, Folder 18)
  - MES 2000-2001 Contracts, Series 3 (Box 67, Folder 19)
  - MES 2000-2001 Brochure, Series 3 (Box 67, Folder 20)
  - MES 2000-2001 Spring Resubscr., Series 3 (Box 67, Folder 21)
  - MES 2000-2001 ThankYous, Series 3 (Box 67, Folder 22)
  - MES 2001-2002, Series 3 (Box 67, Folder 23)
  - MES 2001-2002 Pre Events / Post Events, Series 3 (Box 67, Folder 24)
  - MES 2001-2002 Catering, Series 3 (Box 67, Folder 25)
  - MES 2001-2002 Dinner Letter Menu, Series 3 (Box 67, Folder 26)
  - MES 2001-2002 Correspondence, Series 3 (Box 67, Folder 27)
  - MES 2001-2002 Wash. Post, Series 3 (Box 67, Folder 28)
  - MES 2001-2002 Budget, Series 3 (Box 67, Folder 29)
  - MES 2001-2002 Tax Letters, Series 3 (Box 67, Folder 30)
  - MES 2001-2002 Series Brochure, Series 3 (Box 67, Folder 31)
  - MES 2001-2002 Donation, Series 3 (Box 67, Folder 32)
  - MES Committee Meeting, 2001-2002; Series 3 (Box 67, Folder 33)
  - October 19 FY2002 The Concertante, 2001 October 19; Series 3 (Box 67, Folder 34)
  - November 9 FY2002 Corigliano Quartet, 2001 December 9; Series 3 (Box 67, Folder 35)
  - December 7 FY2002 Kalish-Swensen-Katz Trio, 2001 December 7; Series 3 (Box 67, Folder 36)
  - January 18 FY2002 The Colorado Quartet, 2001 January 18; Series 3 (Box 67, Folder 37)
  - American Chamber Players 2002, Series 3 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Takacs String Quartet 2002, Series 3 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - April 5 FY2002 The Peabody Trio, 2002 April 5; Series 3 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - The Whitman Quartet May 3 FY2002, 2002 May 3; Series 3 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - MES 2002-2003 Table of Contents, Series 3 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - MES 2002-2003 Series, Series 3 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - MES 2002-2003 Contacts Volunteers, Series 3 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - MES 2002-2003 Program Notes, Series 3 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - MES 2002-2003 Pre Events / Post Events, Series 3 (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - MES 2002-2003 Correspondence, Series 3 (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - MES 2002-2003 Catering, Series 3 (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - MES 2002-2003 Tax Letters, Series 3 (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - MES 2002-2003 Washington Post etc., Series 3 (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - MES 2002-2003 Budget, Series 3 (Box 68, Folder 14)
  - MES 2002-2003 Series Brochure, Series 3 (Box 68, Folder 15)
  - 2002-2003 MES, Series 3 (Box 68, Folder 16)
  - MES Committee, 2002-2003; Series 3 (Box 68, Folder 17)
  - October 18, 2002 FY2003 Ying Quartet, 2002 Octoberr 18; Series 3 (Box 68, Folder 18)
  - November 8, 2002 FY2003 St. Lawrence String Quartet, 2002 November 8; Series 3 (Box 68, Folder 19)
  - December 13, 2002 FY2003 Kalish, Swensen, Katz Trio, 2002 December 13; Series 3 (Box 68, Folder 20)
  - January 24, 2003 FY2003 Peabody Trio, 2003 January 24; Series 3 (Box 68, Folder 21)
  - February 27, 2003 FY2003 Takacs Quartet, 2003 February 27; Series 3 (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - March 14, 2003 FY2003 Miro Sting Quartet, 2003 March 14; Series 3 (Box 68, Folder 23)
  - April 18, 2003 FY2003 Gryphon Trio, 2003 April 18; Series 3 (Box 68, Folder 24)
  - MES 2003-2004 Contacts, Series 3 (Box 68, Folder 25)
  - MES 2003-2004 Committee Meetings and Notes, Series 3 (Box 68, Folder 26)
  - MES 2003-2004 Season Subscription, Series 3 (Box 68, Folder 27)
  - MES 2003-2004 Programs and Program Notes, Series 3 (Box 68, Folder 28)
  - MES 2003-2004 Pre Events Post Events, Series 3 (Box 68, Folder 29)
  - MES 2003-2004 Ticket Lists, Series 3 (Box 68, Folder 30)
  - MES 2003-2004 Catering, Series 3 (Box 68, Folder 31)
  - MES 2003-2004 Washington Post, Series 3 (Box 68, Folder 32)
  - MES 2003-2004 Correspondence, Series 3 (Box 68, Folder 33)
  - MES 2003-2004 Tax Letters, Series 3 (Box 68, Folder 34)
  - MES 2003-2004 Budget, Series 3 (Box 68, Folder 35)
  - MES 2003-2004 Series Brochure, Series 3 (Box 68, Folder 36)
  - MES 2004-2005 Contacts, Series 3 (Box 68, Folder 37)
  - MES 2004-2005 Committee Meetings and Notes, Series 3 (Box 68, Folder 38)
  - MES 2004-2005 Schedule / Budget, Series 3 (Box 68, Folder 39)
  - MES 2004-2005 Season Subscription and Promotion, Series 3 (Box 68, Folder 40)
  - MES 2004-2005 Series Brochure, Series 3 (Box 68, Folder 41)
  - MES 2004-2005 Program and Program Notes, Series 3 (Box 68, Folder 42)
  - MES 2004-2005 Ticket Lists, Series 3 (Box 68, Folder 43)
  - MES 2004-2005 Pre Events Post Events, Series 3 (Box 68, Folder 44)
  - MES 2004-2005 Catering, Series 3 (Box 68, Folder 45)
  - MES 2004-2005 Tax Letters, Series 3 (Box 68, Folder 46)
  - MES 2004-2005 Press, Series 3 (Box 68, Folder 47)
  - MES 2004-2005 Correspondence, Series 3 (Box 68, Folder 48)
- Art sales and commissions, 1997-2000; Series 4
  - Buttercup Yellow Persian with Red Lip Wrap (1 of 2), 1997; Series 4 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Buttercup Yellow Persian with Red Lip Wrap (2 of 2), 1997; Series 4 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - The Bad Mother, 1998; Series 4 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - The Other Side of the Moon (1 of 2), 1998; Series 4 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - The Other Side of the Moon (2 of 2), 1998; Series 4 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - No Thank You!, 1999; Series 4 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Coral Basket with Golden Wrap, 1999; Series 4 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Teal Seafoam with Amber Body Wrap, 1998; Series 4 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Wrapped Reischtag Project for Berlin, 2000; Series 4 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Ila Borders, Baseball Player, 1998; Series 4 (Box 36, Folder 10)
- Trips, 1995-1999; Series 5
  - Swinging London Cancelled, 1998 November 14 - 1998 November 20; Series 5 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Hidden Treasures (1 of 2), 1995 September; Series 5 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Hidden Treasures (2 of 2), 1995 September; Series 5 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Documenta and Munster (1 of 2), 1997 June - 1997 July; Series 5 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Documenta and Munster (2 of 2), 1997 June - 1997 July; Series 5 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Vietnam, Cambodia Laos, 1997 February; Series 5 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Around the World in Eight Days Cancelled (1 of 2), 1999 June; Series 5 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Around the World in Eight Days Cancelled (2 of 2), 1999 June; Series 5 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Paris Fashion and Personal Image Consultant (1 of 2), 1998 May - 1998 June; Series 5 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Paris Fashion and Personal Image Consultant (2 of 2), 1998 May - 1998 June; Series 5 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Vail and Aspen Arts, Music and Spa Holiday Cancelled, 1999 August; Series 5 (Box 35, Folder 11)